Jan Werbrouck | Graphics Programmer

janfwerbrouck@gmail.com jan300100.github.io/Portfolio

+44 7544 79 75 32 +32 487 55 10 44

Summary

I grew up in Belgium and learned programming while pursuing a Professional Bachelor's in Game Development. I am a results-oriented programmer with a strong focus on graphics programming, rendering and optimization.

I have a lot of curiosity, creativity, and problem-solving skills, with the ability to pick up new technologies quickly. Experienced in profiling and optimising rendering and memory, as well as reducing loading times.

Relevant Skills

- · C++
- Unreal Engine (C++ & Blueprints)
- · Console Experience: **Xbox One (GCN)** and **Xbox Series (RDNA2)**
- · Modern Graphics APIs: DirectX 12 and Vulkan
- · GPU Profiling tools: Pix, NSight and RenderDoc
- · Shading languages: **HLSL**, **GLSL** and **UE4** materials.

Experience

PROGRAMMER | APRIL 2023 - CURRENT | CLIMAX STUDIOS

JUNIOR PROGRAMMER | SEPTEMBER 2021 - APRIL 2023 | CLIMAX STUDIOS

Worked as a part of the graphics team of the **PC port** of the **PS5** exclusive **Returnal** for **Sony** in Unreal Engine. Fixing shader and material issues, profiling and optimising rendering and memory and loading issues.

Currently working on the optimisation team for another AAA Title for **Microsoft**, profiling and optimising the game for both **Xbox One** and **Series**.

Internship | Februari 2021 - June 2021 | Climax Studios

Programming in Unreal Engine C++ and implementing multiplayer functionality for an early prototype in Unreal Engine. Joined the team working on the **PC Port** of the **PS5** game **Returnal** at the start of the project.

STUDENT JOB | I-SOLV-IT

(joris@isolvit.be | +32 484 95 86 46)

Working on Windows applications, **SQL**, **C#** and **WPF**.

Education

DIGITAL ARTS AND ENTERTAINMENT | 2018 - 2021 | HOWEST - KORTRIJK

· Professional Bachelor in Game Development, focus on Graphics Programming.

Languages

- Dutch Native
- **English** Fluent (C2)